I heartily congratulate and welcome all of them to the channel,
as you can see,
okay, as you can see that today
some of our thumbnails are completely different and
different, so why is it,
you know that if such a thumbnail has been
put, if a woman is
making such a video, then you know that it is an
educator, if there is a problem then only
we would have thought of making this video, so
you all are heartily congratulated and
welcome to our channel, especially
if anyone is watching Tata, which is a
very prestigious company established by Ratan Tata
and which understands the feelings of people, then
definitely watch this video and
try to solve as many problems as you can related to ours, my
main purpose of making this video is
that the common class, which is
not able to buy very expensive cars, expects
that yours should be of this kind, ours should be
very good,
so come on children, without
wasting a single minute, we are starting
this video, okay, we will not spend even a minute watching this video  Let's
start without doing it,
I wonder if you can see me or
hear me, I don't
think you can see me or hear me,
please tell me once
in the video whether you can see me or
not and whether you can hear me or not,
if you can hear me or not, then also it's okay,
all my students have exams now and
in such a situation of exams, we are busy
preparing for you, but in between, a
very big and very amazing problem which was not expected, was not anticipated,
we faced such a
problem for which I had to come live, so
children, I would like to tell you whatever it is,
along with the children, there are other people too, as you
can see in the thumbnail,
that this Tata Navi car was purchased and
after purchasing it, when we put it on the first service, the
serviceman told that there is
some problem in its charging point and there is
some problem in the charging point, I have
all the numbers also, I will provide all these
numbers, if anyone is watching from data then definitely
watch it and try to solve our problem, there
is some problem in it  And they charged 850 for that, for which
I have the bill as well, that there is
something
technical or whatever in your charging point, we do
not understand that much about the car and we paid that at the
time of first service, for which we have the bill also,
when this car went for second service after a few days, then at the
time of going for second service,
we put its charger on charging and when we took it out in the morning,
half of it was inside the car and half outside,
when we took it with the complaint, then
they said that you will have to
buy a new charger, there is no other charger,
and the charger was not for 5-100 Hz, it was a full
0000 charger many times and from here the
main purpose of me buying this car was that in
my job almost daily there is a
run of 100 km, so it
is not possible to run 100 km in any normal car,
so you can imagine if I am
going by taxi, for the last 15 days I have been
going by taxi, then my expenditure is around 000 per day,
so you can imagine that for that 100
km  It has a run and you have to
look at all the other things as well, so we thought
that this would be a very economical car which would
prove to be a panacea for us and would give us a lot of benefit in daily runs,
but when
after the first service, the charger of the car was broken, for this we
went to the service station several times, I will provide you all
the service stations or we
took the car from Aakd Motor Jaipur and after that its first
service was done in VKI Vishwakarma
Industrial Area, for the second service
we were again sent to BKE Vishwakarma
Industrial Area and at that time
its charger got damaged, so
we paid Rs. 0000 for it, then
we had to buy a new charger, that charger of
ours was neither replaced nor repaired, they
said you will have to buy a new charger and along with this,
you should get the insurance done from ICI Lombard, the
insurance company which got it done for us, tell me,
if someone from a middle class family is buying a car by paying such a huge amount, then he must be under some
compulsion and if
you are spending lakhs of rupees on it within six months of buying it, then
what must have
happened to him.  Tata, whose name is there, who
stood with the middle class families,
we did not expect that this kind of
service will be given to us and I know and
I know that this message is not reaching the main employees sitting there,
if
this message reaches them then they will 100%
understand our pain and our problem and
they will try to solve it in some way or the other,
I was
sitting with hope, after this our one day is not over yet,
we paid 50000 chargers,
when the car goes for service then there is a good amount of
free service but free
service is nothing, even after free service
we are still paying for the service,
now this car came after the service and I was
driving it, I am driving it,
see the car
is parked like this, our car is parked like this, I
am on the driving seat, a girl came from here
and she hit from here, hit from here,
my car got unbalanced here, there is
a gate, there was damage from here and
this entire gate got damaged, now
in Tata company when  When this was given to them, they
said this won't happen, this won't happen either,
they only repaired this and gave it to me and I was
helpless to at least get this repaired
otherwise this wouldn't get fixed from outside either, so getting it
repaired from outside was still costing lakhs of rupees,
so they
just repaired this part for us and gave it to us
completely, see here I am
sitting on the driving seat, a girl hit me from here, I got
unbalanced and
put my foot on the rail of the car, there was a stone in front here,
I don't know what it was, it hit this part of our car, this part of
it got completely damaged and along with this part getting
damaged, this
entire gate got damaged because there was a gate here
which the car hit, now I am saying make a
video of the accident and send it, tell me, suppose
someone had an accident 250 kilometers
away, will he
take photos from 250 kilometers away, but still
I asked for photos and sent the photos, so what do you
say, this happened to you at different times,
we are tracing the car, so it means you
also trace the car,
personal information of a person reaches you
because the car  If the
technology has developed in this way, then you are also able to see
which person is going where, so
this is not a bigger issue than this, the leakage of our personal information is happening,
this is not our security,
if you are saying that
you are looking at the car, then in the name of humanity,
you should see, I spoke to a person in ICI Lombard today,
I can give you the number also
and what did he mail on email, I said
that you mail me, I will
go to the consumer court, you mail me that you will
not do this, so the email has come, let me
tell you the email, it is written in two lines that this is all
you will be covered for and I will provide all the numbers,
if someone is from Tata company
then he should listen to us and find a solution,
we do not want to mess with anyone, we do
not want to fight with anyone, we just
want that if you give us a car, then
service it in such a way that the
remaining four people also buy it, you know that
in India, if not today then after 10 years, we have
advanced technology thinking that after 10 years
everyone is going to come, so
Please all of you who are watching, my
viewers, my
cell service jib ji, my experience
jib ji does not matter, neither the
seller cares, nor the insurance company people care,
nor does anyone else care, so I think it's
time to say goodbye, take care, stay
healthy, stay happy, enjoy and my
children, if I talk about reading then keep
reading, so we will talk about the rest
in the next video, we will meet you live tomorrow.